[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Isao Miyoshi is a very clever recycler from Japan. What did he recycle?", "correct_answer": "Dentures", "incorrect_answers": ["Pachinko machines", "Roulette wheels", "Old Macintosh computers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All penguins are found exclusively in the Southern Hemisphere.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The fat is hot enough to fry in when green smoke rises from the pan.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The founder of this German car brand produced the first petrol-powered motorcycle in the world, as well as the first gasoline-powered automobile.", "correct_answer": "Mercedes-Benz", "incorrect_answers": ["BMW", "Porsche", "Opel"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of the Lord of the Rings movies won the Academy Award for Best Picture?", "correct_answer": "The Lord of the Rings: Return of the King", "incorrect_answers": ["The Lord of the Rings: Fellowship of the Ring", "None of them", "The Lord of the Rings: The Two Towers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This tree is a very important part of the Madagascar dry deciduous forests and six species of it are endemic to the island.", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Bottle tree", "Monkey bread tree", "Upside-down tree"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How much money a day was Hedley Lamarr prepared to give to his gang of thugs to destroy the township of Rock Ridge in the movie Blazing Saddles?", "correct_answer": "$100", "incorrect_answers": ["$50", "$150", "$200"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the animated movie Meet the Robinsons, Lewis mother, when leaving him on the step, heard a noise which made her rush away. Later in the movie, we find out what caused this noise. What was it?", "correct_answer": "Lewis", "incorrect_answers": ["A neighborhood kid", "A rat", "Goob"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "It is generally accepted, that economic market systems have proved to be so stable and efficient for which of these reasons?", "correct_answer": "They facilitate exchange and specialization.", "incorrect_answers": ["Everyone pays the same amount in taxes.", "People cannot be self-sufficient.", "Producers cannot specialize without markets."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In James Bonds Goldfinger, Oddjob uses what deadly weapon also used by John Steed in detective series The Avengers?", "correct_answer": "Hat", "incorrect_answers": ["Belt", "Tie", "Shoe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Red is the color of all these except one.", "correct_answer": "Sadness", "incorrect_answers": ["Danger", "Warmth", "Passion"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of animal is the Gold tegu, found in South America?", "correct_answer": "Reptile", "incorrect_answers": ["Insect", "Deer", "Primate"]}]